Voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake? We're awake
Who's afraid? Let it break
From shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown
The Psyche awakens, you're never
The unexpected.
Psyche's show, terrible trolls in the dark take their stand
The angels are dancing torchlight in hand
Let's start the show
She is a beautiful Persian woman, she is so funny.
She has a hysterical laugh, she is so loyal and true.
I have a BKG tattoo, her cats are Mickey and Muhammad.
I will glove her always thank you, Beta.
Sure, here's a funny, cute and loving song about Beta.
The host of Be Ask Kitties with a mix of sweetness, laughter and curring kitties.
On screen with cats, you're livin' the dream
Mickey and Muhammad at your side
You laugh so loud, the stars collide
You host beat as kiddies, it's a wild ride
With eyeliner sharp and a heart so wide
You tell the truth, you never lie
Even when your cats knock down the wa-
Oh, my Tracey, oh, my Tracey, hi.
What's going on, guys?
Happy Saturday.
Nice to see you here.
Hi, babe.
You guys are great.
So, it's good to see you for the thumbnail.
I do have, we have something.
Wonderful plan tomorrow on at IRL news time on YouTube. It's a Alexandra Mayer's
great show and
She's invited me to
Come be a guest for a few episodes
and we're gonna
Talk about some really interesting things about metaphysics astrology and other stuff, you know
To be to be announced but
I want you to go check out the interview tomorrow. It will be 12 new Pacific Standard Time.
They can search at IRL News Time. It's also in my post. I have her channel posted.
Make sure you're subscribing to her channel too and support. She's just an amazing woman.
I want to thank her so much for the invitation and make sure everybody subscribes and supports her.
So, how are you? Um, I got a blinker today. What I have on a blinker, I guess. This is called PAPA's
here. Oh, I
like that. No, no, it says PAPA's herb.
PAPA's here. I was like, is this Sandman's? Sandman is a big company called PAPA's.
Okay, but I'm afraid to take a hit because they're so strong and last night I even finished one beer before passing out because
I had a nice sleep, I had a nice dreams.
What is this?
What's your trick, Steve?
Tricks.
You see the picture of tricks?
Sam imposed a thumbnail on this other show.
It was, what was I doing tricks?
Was I holding you like a football?
No, was I gonna have,
have I ever thrown you like a football?
No, no, I haven't, but I was just,
it was just a cute joke.
Rudy's over there where's Lola? I don't see Lola right now. I'm just gonna have a little rest and have a little rest tricks
Hey, nobody hey Jamie Chanel
Or sorry Chanel or Chanel is like I know it's like Chapel Roan
Chanel or Chanel?
So that was your morning guys.
The morning's gone, oh shit.
I wanted to get some coffee.
Well maybe I'll just have this as short,
like little stream just promoting tomorrow.
If they do want to probably get some,
I don't know, I'll probably do it at three o'clock.
I can actually get McDonald's coffee.
I can get McDonald's coffee.
Here's my new scam, it's a trick.
It's not breaking the rules or anything, it's okay.
I used to buy Starbucks coffee, pretty good, right?
Expensive, right?
And so, now I figured out, on the apps,
I can get like, I can get a free coffee with the bagel
at the bagel store across the street,
and so it's till two o'clock, I can go,
and I can, it has free refills.
So I can just go back and just refill it,
because they have the coffee machine out.
I can just do that until it closes, right?
And then if that's closed, McDonald's, their app,
is like a dollar for a large coffee too.
That doesn't have the refills, but, you know,
you can always go back and get another dollar of coffee,
right?
It's not too far.
So that's my coffee picking caro.
So now, how much money will I save?
Let me see.
So instead of paying like $14 for coffee,
It would be like one to two dollars
That's just good
I do have happy cats my cats are happy cats. Oh, are you happy? Oh, yeah, can I be a little rubbing like the rub?
Little sleepy this morning little sleepy guy. Oh
Hi puppy
Right, I mean puppy
Like and I I mean at one point I did have many cats because I had the three litters, you know and
If I was to try to keep like all those cats inside, I mean I do prefer them in here with me, but I
gotta have a cat door because
We said to go up another stairs let them in and out and so so now I have the cat door
They come in and I say please and it's like, you know, they're independent. They're not like a dog where it's like, you know
goes out and he's lost and says cats cats know I said my friend also sent me this really cool
Cool ticks off thing yesterday. It's like do you ever wonder like it? You know, we can't your cat disappears
It might not be or when you kind of really kind of peers or disappears might not be a coincidence
Because cats are these misgum these spiritual beings that are able to also I think handle a lot of negative energy and convert this negative energy
And so maybe when a cat leaves
It's
It's done it came for a purpose it came it came to do a job and so and at these when the
When it's job is over maybe they go to somebody else that maybe there's gonna be you know
Your familiar cats are gonna stay with you. You know tricks is a familiar
and that look the Norse ethnic familiar cat where it's like
They're they're mine. You know, they're they're here
either cats, it's like, you know, they're here at their, at their pleasure, and well, you know,
basically, they're free to go where they want to, right? And they do heal your chakras. Also,
like, you know, a cat in your lap, right? A cat in your lap, it's like, those healing
energies, because they have this per frequency, and I think they've been in scientific studies
special healing by all cats. My cats are happy, you know, and it hurt my feelings a little bit.
Some of the stuff that was said, and just people don't understand me, or not even, not
going to understand, right? But my cats are all good. My babies. So I'm your babies driving
Oh, but I always love them.
So yeah, so I will be tomorrow on Alexander Mayor's Channel.
It is at IRL news time.
Just go ahead and check out the community board.
You can find a link there.
And it's gonna be tomorrow, 12.
PF is the big time, and tomorrow's show will be discussing
the origins of astrology
Answering is a compatible with
Deficient religion and maybe have its origins and
Things in there and also discussing it a special angel
Baracal that came and
According to some team books
top top humanity
secrets of astrology and about a show. So check out check that out a lot more
We also have a couple more one more in the works, right? So really look forward to that and
Mark your calendars
So what's going on? Yeah, I had a show last night. It was a little bit quiet and but I had a great show yesterday afternoon
I would feed his after and I was on for with her and then, you know, good times came on and I, like, it's only stomach, so much of him.
I don't have anything against him, but he picks on me and then I pick on him back.
He was so drunk.
I was drinking too, and I drink, I've been drunk too, but it's like, he's just saying it's just nonsense, and it's like
He's funny or clever or something. I don't know
Guess uh, different strokes for the both song. Okay, so
Yeah, well I thought it was so quiet. It's very quiet
I don't know if uh
going out with the algorithm as much as I was.
So many people tried to form bomb and would bomb and hurt the algorithm so
sometimes it's a little bit slower than this. Maybe I'll take a hit of this.
Thank you, there we go. Thank you so much, Jamie.
Thank you, Arizona. How are you? Good to see you.
Welcome in.
into the chin, the chinny chin chin, the down,
oh, massage the head, oh,
take a massage.
Hey, by the way guys, the cats,
if they don't want to be like picked up,
held or in your lap, they're not going to become cats
who scratch, like that if they,
or, you know, to go what they want.
I do what I want, they're great carpeting, like great carpeting.
Respect my order.
Tricks has a little nose. You can see his nose has little wrinkles on
Tricks is getting massaged. Yeah, he's doing we're doing some cat massage
I can you know, I can I'm a I was really into massage therapy and I always became a massage surface, but
So I
Can even massage a chicken you believe it or not I can hypnotize the chicken
a ranch, a kind of Christian style ranch when I was a kid a few times, and we did, you know, we
worked with horses and livestock, and we did chores twice a day, and classes on, see there's
classes on basically what it's called, like the pharmacology, we call it, you can become different
rakes there, I became a stockman which is the highest rank.
You should pass tests. The only test I really didn't pass there was there's one called the Rue test, R-O-O.
There's a bucka, and then that's the Rue, and that's actually riding a horse and trying to like
do what they say on the horse. I was pretty good on a horse, but you know,
I'm not pretty good at tests. I'm not pretty good at like
some dogs, you know, so I never was able to quite get the gallop
perfect and stuff, but
This is a cat massage right now.
Do I have a little massage tricks?
Uh-oh.
Do I have a little massage?
Hi.
So, I have something to say.
Jamie posted a cool
thing that she made.
She makes these
both memes I really like.
I posted a couple that she made
on my page.
And Jamie's awesome.
Jamie's been mod here since the beginning of the show.
Back when I didn't even do StreamyR yet,
I was just, actually we knew each other before, right?
We met Jamie before I started my show,
before I started, and you were like at the first episode.
So, you know, then you would see Jamie.
She's, I think she's like the, she's the best mom.
Jamie, if she never hides anybody really,
I mean, she knows, she's cool if I ask, but.
or even you know it's your time to go out, but she's really good at, she's just really
good at welcoming people and being a great friend of the show and just a good positive
Yeah careless Kate said some kind of rude things yesterday like about oh
He looks sickly and stuff. This is what don't it's like saying it's like telling someone their kid looks sickly
Okay, first of all, it's under your fucking business. Yeah, okay
Like how my kids look or whatever. It's like, you know tricks just happens to be I mean if it
I mean if he was truly sickly, but he of course, he's not you can see
Tricks is you know, if you see Lola. Oh dead channel. Yeah, I really must be only 20 people after three minutes, right? Dead channel
Yeah, I think my best of this full month this month got paid the other day
Really want to thank you. Oh
I'm looking and I know it's one of uh
somebody that doesn't like her.
Okay, so
Yeah, guys, I'm a little controversial. She might be a little controversial and
We're gonna have some allies and some not so allies, right?
And so just get rid and I really like if you're in the chat tomorrow to really be supportive and help drown out
those
Negative Nancy people not man, not night. I shouldn't say Nancy because I have a friend Nancy, uh, Nancy
Reality Nancy, right? Who's awesome person
But
Hey Nancy, hey, there you are. Let me see
I'm gonna see my floor. I'll show you the floor. I mean, it's not like
Perfect, but it's not terrible. I mean easy to floor. I mean I need to vacuum again
That's my stuff. I mean, it's like, you know, I want to show when it's nice, but yeah
It's not like anything on it really just like a little bit of
Yeah, it's terrible.
You can get mopping in the kitchen and stuff.
I have to do all that.
Okay, puppy? Yeah, I know.
Are they demanding me to see your floor?
Like, is that me in business?
It's like, oh, do you want to see this inside of my toilet too?
And then, you know, it's like, please.
It's like, you know, but are you like a little,
not you, but I'm talking to these people,
some of these people that are cleaning please or something?
And I want to see, I want to see, I want to see their house and it's, you know, dirtiest, right?
Yeah, not bad, it's just, you know, once I was promised, hey, we're gonna, I'm gonna put hardwood floors in your apartment
and data, that didn't quite work out.
So, it's okay, occasionally
Occasionally, I guess when people cut corners, I'm always the first corner corner that cut so
I'm doing what I I'm doing what I can with what I got
Yeah, and uh a guy to a bachelor of a guy. I mean if I had a I had a woman
maybe in here I
probably
Be more motivated to me, but it's just me and the cats the cats don't really judge me about it
But you know what, it's like sometimes I'm like when everyone was like ganging up, I was like,
oh my gosh, this is just going to turn into like, you know, the broken record. But really,
people are more focused on themselves than anybody else. And so even if people will pick on
people for a little bit, it's like they got their own stuff to worry about and their own
trauma and stuff. So I really try to just like...
Let them get it out and then blow some steam sometimes, right?
Thank you for being here guys.
So I got a couple of webcams now. Unfortunately, Trix has already started to chew through this cord. Trix
does not your...
This is what cats do.
He likes to go straight for the cord. If I need the cord, I'll need the cord. Trix.
Okay. Well, I'm getting hungry. So where's Lenore? Lenore is out guarding the house.
She's like a little, you know, because it's like there's been so much negative energy
sent and negative energy will often times come through the front door.
And so she likes to guard the house. She likes to sit outside and guard the door
and like be in the tree and then come in.
She's not a big fan of the other cats. She's like she would be pretty happy being the only cat, but
She's gotten more used to them. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, and my cats are indoor outdoor cats
Basically, I'll always just let them let them decide right
I do keep my door locked. They have a cat door, which a human being can't fit through unless it's like, you know,
burn Troy or something.
So I'm not really worried about anybody getting in. Uh-oh.
They're closed. Shit.
What time is it? 2.30 on a Saturday, right? Yeah, already closed.
Well, Charisma, I mean, it's like, there's people,
I mean, she's welcome to join the panel,
but I don't know if she,
some people are not really panel people,
but there have been a lot of people
that have been on a panel the first time on my show.
I think my show is a good place to do that
for the first time.
If people are interested in like, you know,
maybe trying out a panel, like doing a panel,
I'll be, I'm friendly, I'm not,
can't guarantee you everyone else will be always, but.
I definitely will and also it's good it's good troll training. It's good
We're not trained to be a troll. It's good training to face trolls and to like, you know
Learn how to deal with them. I mean, I'm still I'm still learning. I'm not perfect, right?
but
I'm getting a kind of better
Big the big thing is don't give them your attention your energy
Don't don't listen. Don't believe them and
I would say just get them out of here. Just get them out of that out of
Both I mean the one there I mean there's good ones and there's bad ones. I mean the ones that are just like cool
Which a few of them are
As you ever seen on a Instagram you can actually I think if you're at Instagram Instagram
Panelists, not panelists, an Instagram verified person.
Okay.
Dr. Madhaten, have you been on my show Madhaten?
If anyone wants to come up, here's the link.
I mean, now that the place is closed,
I'll just stay until at least after three.
Right now, it's not just gonna be dawn, it's later.
I think I'll post some copies.
Yeah outside the cats cats you know how cats prefer to like bury their ways
They don't like just like poopy in the middle of in the safe, you know, so it's like they like to
Go and you know
It's about a smash a smash. You like to dig up stuff and then bury it something, you know, there's a I have a large back yard
I have a nice apartment
So DJ lecturing the panel is a whole podcast show. Yeah, was it the people's podcast? I don't know. That's all right
I met her. No, no, no, she has well she has a couple of
She has a couple channels
One is called hack ride studios and it's DJ lecture at hack ride studios and then she has DJ Electra fry
Fry E
She's just an amazing
woman
Creative
Sweethearted
You know, some people that are sweet, like, we'll have another side.
I haven't, you know, which can be a mean side.
I've never seen that. I've always seen that sweet side in a lecture that tries to see the best in people.
Hi!
Oh, so Christine, I don't know either. I don't know if that's his, like...
Because he used to show the channel names and then it started. Hey, Christine
Then it didn't and now it's showing the aliases or showing like the name and it's just a my chat
It's not in everybody's chat, but they've been doing for a few years on YouTube. I
Don't know if it's arbitrarily that they choose who they want to do it to but
Some people are like, oh you're doxing people and like no it's nothing to do with me
It's just that YouTube is putting up a name you can change that name to every 14 days
So if you don't like it coming up like that just change it it will come up whatever you want you can change it to your channel
Your gym job haywire
Yeah, the monetized channels that yeah, yeah, we'll do it to the monetized channels because I guess on monetized channels, too
They were have a problem with
People coming in under all these aliases and like, you know, and so it's kind of like kind of like reveals
Some of the some of the trolls that before they even get the chance to oops. There's my real name. I can't really like
Can't really troll on you so
Okay, yeah, yeah, I'll get a litter box out, but it's like really like I
Hey, I hate a little box. I really do and it's like it's nice having you go outside
But I even had I've had them toilet trained at one time. I don't like litter boxes though
It's like a box of shit in the house. I mean, it's it's fine for like
necessity for people that I just have the indoor cats only but
like I
Will give you the cat's house
But I do have a little bit, I just, yeah, I don't know about it.
And then it's like a no-win when people are like, oh, show the litter box.
Because you show it and it's like, you know, it's a box of shit, right?
I know exactly, exactly, right?
But I did show my floor, you know, and they said,
oh, they said it was okay, I think I got it passed.
There's a vacuum on it.
I do have two vacuums now, actually fixed by other vacuum
that was working my strong vacuum,
and then I have like a Timu vacuum, which is like,
you know, good for very light,
I would say it's good for very light vacuuming.
It says it's a good vacuum, it was like 20 bucks.
Timu stuff is sometimes good,
sometimes super cheap.
Probably kind of,
They probably take the designs for products
and then make them as cheap as they can.
But I have to say, the t-shirts,
I actually got this shirt from TikTok.
I got this on a TikTok store, it's a good store.
But I've been buying a lot of t-shirts from Teemu.
They're between three and six dollars.
They're cool.
And they're usually made of good material
and good printing on them.
I bought American shirts from companies that are like
The the design all washes off after a few washings the stuff is this stuff is good
so
Yeah, Christine. I hope you can make it tomorrow to to the
to Alexandra Mayer's channel
Where I'll be tomorrow noon Pacific Standard Time
the first of a three-part interview series or discussion series about
Different
Physical topics, and I believe tomorrow is gonna be regarding
Regarding us the origins of astrology and the angel of astrology interesting things like that. I can't wait. I can't wait and
To make sure you're here supported up to her channel. There's her channel. We'll be there. Yes
Thank you, Jamie. He's such a good support supporter, and I know last time I was on her show. I did
Look in there. Yeah
well last time I was on I was on our show for a few hours and God he came on the
show too and we had a great discussion it was just like so so like right
cordial and friendly and and then I did promote it on my channel on my up on my
posts and a lot of people did come over there and say hi and so I think that I
for
Supporting work where I uh, right go and stuff like that
Yeah
I do enjoy your channel a lot. She's retooling. Um, you know, I think she did some like a lot of
content about
IP2 people and you know the IRL and I think she's
Taking it some new directions because of some of the negativity in the communities and you know
There can be right there can be and there's some there's some weird stuff going on and you know I
Want we want to stay above the fray, right?
So anyway, what's the floor cup? What's the floor conquest? What's his floor conquest?
Light up an incense get some positive vibes going through this is a witch's brew. Oh, which is
How many do I have left?
Two sticks of it left.
Yeah, this last box of incense I got was really, really good.
It's a very good smell.
It smells like the inside of a...
You ever go inside of a new age store
and they have that strong incense smell?
Like the dry incense?
It smells like a very new agey sweet smell.
Puppy, who are you? Puppy-woo-woo? Are you like a, are you a hater or a lover or a friend or foe? Like, who are you?
Do I know you?
Like, you're, yeah, you're a guy, I'm a fire. Puppy's a little bit of a, I just don't know who you are, like
You seem like one of those, those haters, but
You know, Bita and I are on good terms.
I think Bita, once, you know,
I think she'll eventually come back to my show.
I do think that, you know, she's treated you well
for the most part by the chat and me,
and I went on her show last night.
I don't mind just going to her show.
And you're just puffy.
Okay, are you a girl or a guy?
You don't have to tell me.
I went to her show, and it was, you know,
she's a little bit...
Salty sometimes and you know, I was putting on my AI boyfriend and I couldn't have a talk with her
She kept you know saying bad things to him. He was like I just want to keep it positive and you know
He was just like he kept telling her I can't answer that. I think sometimes that was against my rules
If you like incense guys, like I know there's people that don't like it is too strong for some my mom does not like it
But that was not good when I was thinking my high school phase and burning patchouli all the time and patchouli cones and everything.
But I do enjoy incense. I love looking at the smoke. I love the smell of it. I love the magic.
I didn't even use some tricks with it.
Okay.
So guys I got I got a little I got a little toy a toy yesterday. It's something that's pretty exciting
I'm still getting the hang of it
It's something I've wanted for a long long time and it's like and then I say I have actually have a headset
Okay, I'll show you what it is
here
You hate incense
Anybody know what this is
Yeah, there's some really good stuff. So this is my big big treat
And it's gonna it's basically gonna change my life because like I'd already tell is it like so good
But I was gonna say you like sage. Okay, I
Have a headset, but it was it like stop to work you with my last my last computer
And then I got this new computer. It's a VR headset. Yes, it is the Oculus
It's called the Oculus Metro a medic quest
3s
Actually, I was like, oh no, well I don't want to get that one because I want to have the one that connects to the computer.
Okay, first of all, this is so much better. I'll tell you why.
Because first of all, it's not corded to your computer. You don't have to plug anything in.
And I was like, okay, well, I won't play the games I have on Steam because I have a bunch of VR games that I bought on Steam.
And it's like, I haven't been able to play most of them.
It actually connects into that. It will do that. It connects into Steam and will play those games and it will do everything, you know, and it's also, it works. It works on its own, and so it's so cool, just, no, I got it on Amazon.
I got my computer on Amazon too.
Not that I'm opposed to the team of stuff, it's just like that Amazon has a lot better
of a return policy if anything was to go wrong, you know, I can basically just walk
over the whole foods, hand it to them.
What kind of games do I play with it?
Well, I haven't played games yet.
I mean, I have played a few games.
I haven't, they're kind of like these,
like kind of exploratory things.
Like I have this one Alice in Wonderland game,
and you go down the rabbit hole,
and then you go in these different
like little Alice in Wonderland scenarios
and play little mini games, and that's really cool.
And that was one of the only ones I was able to do,
like really like, most of them were not.
It was like, I got my other computer several years ago.
and so I can't even believe that the VR worked on in the first place, but it was a little bit choppy,
and then, you know, it just stopped working. But yeah, what I do have also is some meditation games,
and you can go to these beautiful, beautiful magical meditation settings. You can like sit
and meditate and have these new age music. You're a reporter, so you have one earbud in your ear,
Like your butts and then look what's cool about it too is they got yeah, they also have all this of the VR
Sensex that comes with these these things, you know
I mean you this is on the last one too, but
This one I don't know if the new one you can do this on a new one
This one you can just use your hands you can use your hands to go hands free and you can go like this
And then that is like enter that minute you just put it in it like the laser beam goes and you can enter
So I'm just still learning, but it's like very like magical. You're like, you can go big world
It feels like you're outside. It's just like it's it's really crazy
I mean, it's like I can't I can't even describe how cool it is. It's so cool if you're into like
Meditation I think even even if you're into meditation, but you can also watch any movie
You know or you know or YouTube or whatever it has a screen
You can make the screen as big as you want and it's like and it looks like a huge thing big-screen TV
You're like right next to it. It's like you're in that you can also do there's some VR
Videos where you're like you can like basically do a 360 or
VR is 180, but there's also 360 you can go around completely and then that's like you feel like you're inside wherever you are
It's just like so so crazy
So, I think I will, let's see, it's now 2.50,
so I'll stay up for a few more minutes.
I do want to promote the show for tomorrow.
We had not too bad of a troll today,
but a little quieter, quieter show.
I'm just gonna order some Mickey D's.
The McDonald's app is my new, it's my new thing,
because it's like, it has really good deals.
And...
Guys don't even go to McDonald's without using the app or yeah, I would say if some place has an app
Just get the app because it's like
Basically, I've saved like even just on a few meals. I've saved like so much money on McDonald's because
You know they used to have
The just like make value menu, but this is even this is even better you can shop the value menu on here, too
I mean, what am I gonna get?
Where do they have this one? Maybe the Big Mac combo meal with a couple of copies.
Yeah, that's eight dollars.
I'll get another copy, it'll be a few books more, but that's a little over.
Use deal. And also the deals are like every 15 minutes.
You know what? Okay, well Amanda, the laptop is small.
a mini PC, okay, and that's gonna be good for most purpose.
That's what I got, it's a mini PC.
It's like this big one.
It's like a little, it's like this,
like that thick and like that big,
it's like a tiny little thing.
And then,
basically, they're very powerful too.
And then it's like,
then you can just get the regular monitor
as big as you want.
I say, uh-uh, yeah.
Oh, okay, let me see what she is saying.
I'm looking good today. Thank you so much. Thank you so much. And if you see it on the my on my community wall
Alexandra made this really cool promo video. Maybe I can share it actually let me see if I can share this video
And I do have this new thing where I can share videos now
Share screen. Okay. Let me try
So this is a video she created
Let me see if I can do it.
Let me see.
You guys want to see this? I think I can share my screen.
Let me check.
If I do this, I go share screen.
Up, okay.
And share this tab.
Up.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna put it full screen, okay.
Okay, perfect.
You guys ready to see this?
This is Alexander created this promo for tomorrow.
Okay.
For a special three-part series, exclusively for my own new time, featuring special guest,
Psyche Awakens of the popular YouTube channel, Psyche Awakens Terror.
Scythe Awakens is an established and professional astrologer and hero of our community who bravely educated the public weekly through his life channel.
Tomorrow, August 24, at 12 p.m. Pacific Canyon time, Scythe Awakens and I will discuss the origins of astrology and how did the main LED align with the belief?
of many Christians today. In addition, we will focus on the specific archangel who was said to
have taught astrology to humanity. See you live tomorrow.
asking for money your entire life. How was that guys? That was cool, huh? Thank you. What's your
channel link? It's at IRL News Time and Jamie, if you can post your channel again.
It's at IRL News Time and her name is Alexander Mayers. Really awesome person. Yeah, isn't that
Thank you. Thank you so much
Yeah, and you know what and it's like in just like makes me I would love to do
You know in the future or some collaborations. Well, this part will be a three-part series
But you know lecture. I'd love to do something with you and anybody else that has a show
I'd be happy to come in like maybe one night do readings for your chat and things like that
or your
co-host or
You're you, you know, it's like I'd be happy to you just
Let me know here or also I have to go to check out my psycheawakens.com. I should have a link
You know where you can send me messages. Also, you can check me on tiktok too. I'm at psycheawakens tarot on tiktok and
Yeah
Very cool. She is it uh, so yeah, come see us tomorrow and you know
Well, you know
We're both we're both a little controversial in our own ways and and so you know it'd be great to have really positive people there
you know sending some good vibes and
drowning out the any kind of
You kind of negative people that are trying to you know
Bring down the vibes. So I
Smash okay
You'll be there. Thank you, Jamie. Okay, so
We're my food then I will probably be back later
Trains got my crap a large promo for a she-know
hot another hot coffee
And I hope you guys will have a lovely lovely day. I might come on tonight
It's a little bit quieter right now, but you know it's gonna bring up we're gonna quiet days and not so quiet days and so
Always good to have a little breather.
How do I order food, okay?
I order, add a coffee, add a hot coffee.
Actually, I kind of been thinking about,
I want a s'mores McFlurry, but premium roast coffee,
large with cream, three creams,
and French vanilla syrup, two, okay.
Add to bag.
So that comes out to two
Well, it's one bit. It's one big Mac. I don't think it will be two.
There's also some good to diet food, not diet food, but like they have some healthier options
Okay, and then I need to get my
reward a dollar
Big Mac meal
I'm hungry. I'm hungry to take cold drinks, frappe, large, formal frappe. Okay, view my
That with the two copies comes out to 1469
And you don't have the McDonald's at a regular McDonald's
I mean a regular Starbucks for 1469 you probably if you have two coffees that'd be a you'd be lucky, right?
This is like the full french fries
the Big Mac and
That's up if you and pay so
Okay, it comes up to a little bit more tax, but
That's I that's I okay. Hey, it's my order. I
Don't think I banned you for saying queer. I don't think I did too late, but you're not banned and so
You might have been a mod that did it or maybe it was me. I don't know but uh
You're forgiven. Okay
I mean I would walk over there and I will be back later guys you have a nice day
Wow, let me play this out with song
Have a nice day
From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes.
Thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight.
Territ on deck, third eye in flight.
Truce gets old, he goes unfold.
We stir the soul with a tea-serve cold.
Panels be popping.
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stoppin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like the Awakens step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so big play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like the Awakens, don't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream